== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
(Sheldon:)Thank you for coming by,
gentlemen.
(Howard:)No problem.
So what's up?
(Sheldon:)Well, it was the two of you who
found Amy Farrah Fowler for me.
(Sheldon:)Now that I'm looking
for my next girlfriend,
(Sheldon:)it seemed only logical that I
employ your services once again.
Y-You sure you're up for that?
She did hurt you.
(Sheldon:)Oh, no, it's all right.
I think of my time with Amy
as a stick of Fruit Stripe gum:
sweet and enjoyable at first,
(Sheldon:)but ultimately
a flavorless lump of sadness.
(Raj:)You're not wrong
about Fruit Stripe.
I-I was always
a Hubba Bubba man. Mm.
(Howard:)Hubba Bubba over Dubble Bubble?
You're crazy.
(Raj:)Hey, the jaw wants
what it wants.
Gentlemen!
(Raj:)Oh, right, uh, girlfriend. Okay.
(Howard:)But what are you
looking for?
(Sheldon:)All I'm looking for
(Sheldon:)is an educated, intelligent
woman who shares my interests
(Sheldon:)while retaining
her own unique point of view.
(Sheldon:)She should be kind,
(Sheldon:)patient,
(Sheldon:)and most important,
(Sheldon:)unable to imagine life
without me by 10:00 tonight.